A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07300739), 1973 October 02-1974 October 01 (Reel R1090)
    PROGRAM TO EXTEND APPLICATION OF FRONTIERO DECISION REGARDING SEX DISCRIMINATION
    Berresford, Susan V. (Susan Vail);Roditti, Esther C.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07350663), 1973 August 15-1974 August 14 (Reel R2821)
    SUPPORT FOR MIDDLE EASTERN PROFESSOR ON THE UNIVERSITY STAFF
    $23,077.00;$23,077.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07400267), 1974 April 01-1976 June 30 (Reel R2215)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A SEMINAR IN HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING DIRECTED TOWARD FRENCH-SPEAKING COUNTRIES OUTSIDE FRANCE
    Population [POP];Africa & The Middle East [AME]
    $28,380.00;$28,253.99
    Harkavy, Oscar;Horovitz, Richard A.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07400448), 1974 July 01-1976 December 31 (Reel R2976)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON IMPROVING MANPOWER UTILIZATION IN LOCAL GOVERNMENT
    $50,000.00;$49,673.07
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07400468), 1974 July 01-1977 June 30 (Reel R2211)
    SUPPORT FOR THE COLUMBIA JOURNAL OF ENVIRONMENTAL LAW
    $13,120.00;$13,120.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07400594), 1974 July 01-1979 December 31 (Reel R3580)
    STUDY OF THE ROLE OF ENGINEERS IN ADVANCED INDUSTRIAL SOCIETIES
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07400616), 1974 July 01-1979 December 31 (Reel R2340)
    SUPPORT OF THE "COLUMBIA JOURNALISM" REVIEW
    $505,000.00;$505,000.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07450575), 1974 September 01-1977 August 31 (Reel R1234)
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07500094), 1974 November 01-1978 March 31 (Reel R4055)
    CONFERENCE ON "FUTURE DIRECTIONS FOR GRADUATE INTENATIONAL AFFAIRSEDUCATION"
    $16,730.00;$16,730.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07500396), 1975 June 15-1977 May 31 (Reel R1299)
    FOR FINANCIAL AID TO MINORITY STUDENTS AT THE GRADUATE LEVELS IN THE SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM
    Education and Public Policy;National Affairs [NA];Office of Communications (pre 1979)
    Cooney, Thomas E.;Streibert, Catherine
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07500454), 1975 January 01-1976 December 31 (Reel R1245)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR EDITORIAL AND MISCELLANEOUS COSTS OF PUBLIC PAPERS OF THE SECRETARIES-GENERAL OF THE UNITED NATIONS
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07500504), 1975 August 01-1979 July 31 (Reel R4412, Reel R4413)
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07500516), 1975 July 01-1986 June 30 (Reel R5265)
    SUPPORT FOR NEW YORK-BASED SEMINAR ON ARMS CONTROL AND INTERNATIONAL SECURITY
    $60,000.00;$43,241.90
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07550062), 1974 November 01-1975 September 30 (Reel R1256)
    SUPPORT FOR THE SOUTHERN ASIAN INSTITUTE'S TWO NATIONAL SEMINARS ON PAKISTAN
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07550417), 1975 June 03-1976 June 02 (Reel R1219)
    SUPPORT INST. OF NUTRITION FOR TWO STUDIES ON POSSIBLE CONNECTION BETWEEN INFANT & EARLY CHILDHOOD MALNUTRITION, DEVELOP. & BEHAVIOR
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07600010), 1975 October 01-1976 September 30 (Reel R1529)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A MEETING OF EDITORS AND JOURNALISTS FROM THE U.S., ITALY AND SEVERAL OTHER EUROPEAN COUNTRIES
    $18,300.00;$18,300.00
    Europe, Southern
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07600027), 1975 July 01-1978 June 30 (Reel R4236)
    HARVARD-COLUMBIA RUSSIAN STUDIES FUND (ENDOWMENT SUPPORT OF THE RUSSIAN INSTITUTE)
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07600083), 1975 December 04-1977 September 03 (Reel R2879)
    STUDIES OF LONG-RANGE FISCAL AND ECONOMIC PROBLEMS OF NEW YORK CITY
    $200,000.00;$196,307.34
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07600247), 1975 October 01-1979 September 30 (Reel R2952)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR THE COUNCIL FOR EUROPEAN STUDIES TRAINING PROGRAM
    $22,845.95;$22,845.95
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07650337), 1976 June 01-1977 May 31 (Reel R3865, Reel R4277, Reel R4611, Reel R1249)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT ON THE UNIVERSITY AND SOCIAL CHANGE IN CHILE
    Himes, James R.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07650510), 1976 September 01-1978 August 31; Columbia University (Reel R2732)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON "U.S. NON PROLIFERATION STRATEGY AND THE TRANSFER OF NUCLEAR TECHNOLOGY: THE MULTINATIONAL APPROACH
    $22,000.00;$16,418.59
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07750158), 1976 September 01-1977 August 31 (Reel R1299)
    TO COVER THE PURCHASE AND DISTRIBUTION OF THE PUBLICATION "AUTO WORK AND ITS DISCONTENTS" TO SPECIALISTS IN INDUSTRIAL RELAT
    $1,310.00;$1,310.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07750349), 1977 April 01-1977 September 30 (Reel R1309)
    TO DETERMINE THE IMPACT OF TRANSFER PAYMENTS ON THE ECONOMY OF NEW YORK CITY WITH EMPHASIS ON THE PUBLIC POLICY IMPLICATIONS
    $24,956.00;$23,746.58
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07750370), 1977 July 01-1978 June 30 (Reel R1270)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY OF THE POSSIBLE EFFECT OF EARLY NUTRITION ON SUBSEQUENT BEHAVIOR
    $8,400.00;$8,400.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07750689), 1977 July 01-1978 June 30 (Reel R2903)
    FOR A STUDY OF FOSTER PLACEMENT, MALNUTRITION AND ENVIRONMENT
    $12,600.00;$12,600.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07800034), 1977 July 01-1978 June 30 (Reel R1225)
    TO PROVIDE PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE DUPONT-COLUMBIA BROADCAST JOURNALISM SURVEYS AND AWARDS
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07800073), 1978 July 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R3646)
    DEVELOPMENT OF A TRAINING PROGRAM FOR NARRATIVE FICTION FILMMAKERS
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07800078), 1977 December 13-1980 December 12 (Reel R4688)
    SUPPORT OF RESEARCH PROGRAM ON SEX ROLES AND SOCIAL CHANGES
    Education & Culture Program [EC];International - Office of the Vice President [ID/OVP];European and International Affairs
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07800565), 1978 June 01-1979 May 31 (Reel R2384)
    SUPPORT FOR EXPLORATORY STUDY OF PUBLIC EXPENDITURES ON CHILDREN IN NEW YORK CITY
    $25,000.00;$24,903.53
    Kelly, James A.;Lynch, Barbara D.;Saario, Terry
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07800911), 1978 July 01-1980 June 30 (Reel R2887, Reel R2888)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY TO EXPLORE THE RELATIONSHIP OF EARLY NUTRITIONTO CHILD DEVELOPMENT AND SOCIAL ADJUSTMENT
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07850166), 1978 March 01-1980 March 14 (Reel R2963)
    SUPPT TO ENABLE THE SCHL OF LAW TO PARTICIPATE AS A COOPERATING SPONSOR OF THE INDIAN SEMINAR ON THE NEWS MEDIA, LAW AND GOVT....
    $37,673.00;$37,673.00
    Friendly, Fred W.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07850222), 1978 February 01-1978 September 30 (Reel R1401)
    SUPPORT FOR THE ORGANIZATION AND CONDUCT OF HUMAN RIGHTS ACTIVITIES
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07850555), 1978 June 01-1979 May 31 (Reel R3050)
    TO EXAMINE THE SIZE AND ECONOMIC IMPACT OF TAX EXPENDITURES AND TRANSFER PAYMENTS ON THE ECONOMY OF NEW YORK CITY AND HOUSTON
    $24,500.00;$24,428.24
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07850559), 1978 June 01-1979 May 31 (Reel R2715)
    ANALYSIS OF NEW YORK CITY'S LONG-TERM POLICIES TO BE CONDUCTED BY THE CONSERVATION OF HUMAN RESOURCES PROJECT
    $25,000.00;$22,809.67
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07850663), 1978 June 01-1980 October 31 (Reel R2319)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR CONFERENCE ON FOREIGN POLICY AND SECURITY IMPLICATIONS OF A CHANGING EUROPE
    $22,935.00;$22,935.00
    Ruof, Peter;Schoettle, Enid C. B.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07900057), 1978 October 01-1983 December 31 (Reel R4313)
    TO SUPPORT EXCHANGES CONCERNED WITH THE ARTS WITH THE PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC OF CHINA
    Education & Culture Program [EC];Asia & The Pacific [ASIA]
    Cary, Linn F. C.;Geithner, Peter F.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07900279), 1979 March 01-1980 February 28 (Reel R2805, Reel R3053)
    SUPPORT FOR CONSERVATION OF HUMAN RESOURCES PROGRAM TO PRODUCE A VOLUME ANALYZING GOVERNMENT TRAINING AND JOB CREATION PROGRAMS
    $49,000.00;$48,625.56
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07900494), 1979 January 01-1985 January 31 (Reel R4673)
    SUPPORT TO THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF HUMAN RIGHTS
    International - Office of the Vice President [ID/OVP];Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ]
    Bushey, Bruce;Marks, Stephen P.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07900565), 1979 September 01-1981 December 31 (Reel R3648)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A PROJECT ON THE STUDY OF THE AGING PROCESS AND CHANGING SEX ROLES TO BE CONDUCTED BY BETTY FRIEDAN
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07950009), 1979 January 01-1979 September 30 (Reel R3066)
    TO COMPLETE A COMPARATIVE ANALYSIS OF THE YOUTH LABOR FORCE IN TWELVE ADVANCED INDUSTRIAL COUNTRIES
    $15,862.00;$15,862.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07950046), 1978 October 01-1980 May 31 (Reel R2263)
    STUDY OF SEX DIFFERENCES IN CAREER CHOICE AND PLANNING AMONG PRE ADOLESCENT MALES AND FEMALES
    Lynch, Barbara D.;Saario, Terry
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (07950230), 1979 March 01-1979 August 31 (Reel R2164, Reel R2165)
    TRAVEL OF EUROPEAN PARTICIPANTS TO THE MARCH 1979 CONFERENCE OF EUROPEANISTS SPONSORED BY THE COUNCIL FOR EUROPEAN STUDIES
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08000047), 1979 November 01-1980 September 30 (Reel R3051)
    SUPPORT OF A SINO AMERICAN CONFERENCE ON INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS AND THE SOVIET UNION
    China; Soviet Union
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050116), 1979 October 15-1981 June 15 (Reel R2705)
    SUPPORT OF A STUDY OF THE SOUTH BRONX LABOR MARKET
    $5,146.00;$4,980.01
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050173), 1979 December 01-1980 May 31 (Reel R2363)
    SUPPORT FOR A PLANNING SESSION FOR A HUMAN RIGHTS TEACHER TRAININGINSTITUTE
    $3,950.00;$3,950.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050216), 1979 December 31-1981 May 31 (Reel R2287)
    TO ENABLE THE SCHOOL OF LAW TO PARTICIPATE AS A COOPERATING SPONSOR OF THE SOUTH ASIAN SEMINARS ON MEDIA, GOVERNMENT/THE LAW
    $29,061.00;$29,061.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050400), 1980 March 01-1981 February 28 (Reel R2878)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE PREPARATION OF "SETTING MUNICIPAL PRIORITIES, 1981" BY THE CONSERVATION OF HUMAN RESOURCES PROJECT
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050406), 1980 March 01-1981 July 31 (Reel R5495)
    DESIGN AND IMPLEMENTATION OF A MAJOR RESEARCH EFFORT TO DETERMINE THE ROLE OF LEGAL AND ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS ON THE US ECONOMY
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050509), 1980 April 01-1981 February 28 (Reel R4012)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR SYMPOSIUM ON "EAST EUROPE AND THE THIRD WORLD"HELD MAY 2, 1980
    $1,500.00;$1,480.14
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050589), 1980 June 01-1982 September 01 (Reel R4094)
    COLLABORATIVE PROJECT BETWEEN THE CUBAN MINISTRY OF HEALTH AND THECENTER FOR POPULATION AND FAMILY HEALTH
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050604), 1980 July 01-1981 June 30 (Reel R3678)
    SUPPORT FOR AN ANALYSIS OF CHILDREN'S SERVICES IN NEW YORK CITY'S BUDGET
    $25,000.00;$24,964.82
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08050697), 1980 August 01-1981 January 31 (Reel R3076)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A SYMPOSIUM ON ADOLESCENT NUTRITION
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08100405), 1981 March 01-1989 June 30 (Reel R7314, Reel R7559)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT (INCLUDING RECOVERABLE GRANT) FOR THE MEDIA AND SOCIETY SEMINARS
    Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Education & Culture Program [EC];International Affairs Program [IA];US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP]
    $1,635,000.00;$1,635,000.00
    United States; Mass media--Social aspects--United States; Armed Forces and mass media--United States
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08100696), 1981 August 01-1984 March 31 (Reel R4855)
    SUPPORT FOR A SEMINAR ON SECURITY POLICIES OF SOUTH ASIA
    $28,710.00;$28,710.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150165), 1980 October 01-1981 March 31 (Reel R4339)
    INTERNATIONAL TRAVEL COSTS OF PARTICIPANTS TO CONFERENCE IN NEW DELHI ON EXERCISE OF INCOME TAX JURISDICTION OVER CITIZENS ABROAD
    $15,750.00;$14,399.82
    Shad, Shekhar
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150205), 1981 January 01-1981 December 31 (Reel R4062, Reel R4455, Reel R4456)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE PREPARATION OF "SETTING MUNICIPAL PRIORITIES 1982" BY THE CONSERVATION OF HUMAN RESOURCES PROJECT
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150222), 1981 January 01-1982 April 30 (Reel R4382)
    SUPPORT FOR ANNOTATION & TRANSLATION OF MATERIALS IN UNIVERSITY'S ARCHIVES OF POLISH AND ROMANIAN DISSIDENT PUBLICATIONS
    Poland; ROmania
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150430), 1981 May 01-1982 April 30 (Reel R3760)
    SUPPORT FOR THE BARGAINING GROUP'S CONFERENCE ON "BEHAVIORAL APPROACHES TO RESEARCH IN INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS"
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150435), 1981 April 15-1982 April 14 (Reel R3701)
    SUPPORT AMERICAN TRAVEL TO CHINA FOR CONFERENCE ON INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS COSPONSORED WITH CHINESE ACADEMY OF SOCIAL SCIENCES
    $12,612.00;$12,612.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150515), 1981 May 15-1983 June 30 (Reel R5774)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR LAW EXCHANGES WITH THE EAST CHINA INSTITUTE OF LAW AND POLITICS, SHANGHAI
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150586), 1981 May 20-1981 November 19 (Reel R3009)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR COLLOQUIUM ON "PREVENTING ADOLESCENT PREGNANCY: THE ROLE OF THE FAMILY," JUNE 1981
    Teitelbaum, Michael S.
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08150639), 1981 September 01-1982 December 31 (Reel R3611)
    SUPPORT FOR LECTURE SERIES ON N.Y.C. WATERFRONT COMMEMORATING THE CENTENNIAL OF UNIVERSITY GRADUATE SCHOOL OF ARCHITECTURE/PLANNING
    $10,000.00;$9,624.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08200341), 1981 July 01-1992 January 31 (Reel R6136)
    CORE SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER FOR UNITED STATES-CHINA ARTS EXCHANGE
    Education & Culture Program [EC];Developing Country Programs [DCP]
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08200346), 1982 January 01-1991 June 30 (Reel R6180, Reel R6181)
    FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN THE COMBINED SOVIET/EAST EUROPEAN AND INTERNATIONAL SECURITY STUDIES
    $1,347,736.00;$1,347,736.00
    Soviet Union; Europe, Eastern; Global
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08200752), 1982 July 01-1989 May 31 (Reel R5996)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF ADMINISTRATIVE EXPENSES FOR THE PACIFIC BASIN STUDIES PROGRAM
    $403,400.00;$403,400.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08200790), 1982 July 01-1983 September 30 (Reel R5147)
    SUPPORT FOR A COORDINATED SET OF STUDIES AND POLICY ANALYSIS ON THE WORKING POOR
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08200907), 1982 September 01-1986 August 29 (Reel R5121)
    SUPPORT OF PROGRAM IN WASHINGTON HEIGHTS, NEW YORK CITY TO IMPROVE HEALTH STATUS OF DISADVANTAGED INFANTS & YOUNG CHILDREN & PARENTS
    $412,500.00;$412,500.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08201079), 1982 October 20-1989 October 19 (Reel R6360)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND EXCHANGE ACTIVITIES ON DIARRHEAL INFANT MORTALITY IN CUBA
    $606,000.00;$606,000.00
    Heisler, Michele
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250308), 1981 October 01-1982 December 31 (Reel R4155)
    TO EVALUATE RESEARCH PRIORITIES IN HUMAN RIGHTS
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250342), 1982 January 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R4217)
    CONFERENCE ON "POLES AND JEWS: MYTH AND REALITY IN THE HISTORICAL CONTEXT" TO BE CONVENED BY THE INSTITUTE ON EAST CENTRAL EUROPE
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250443), 1982 January 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R4124)
    SUPPORT OF A CONFERENCE TO STUDY THE QUESTION OF COVERAGE OF THE THIRD WORLD BY THE AMERICAN MEDIA
    $24,477.00;$24,477.00
    United States; Southern Hemisphere
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250454), 1982 January 01-1982 December 31 (Reel R4233)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE PREPARATION OF "SETTING MUNICIPAL PRIORITIES 1983"
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250570), 1982 April 06-1982 October 05 (Reel R4375)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF FACULTY COSTS FOR A MUNICIPAL LAW CLINICAL PROGRAM
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250598), 1982 March 01-1983 February 28 (Reel R4856)
    SUPPORT FOR A MEETING TO DISCUSS THE PROBLEMS AND DIFFERENCES WHICH CURRENTLY PLAGUE U.S.-CUBAN RELATIONS
    $7,800.00;$5,017.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250642), 1982 May 01-1984 June 30 (Reel R4228)
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250832), 1982 July 01-1983 June 30 (Reel R4046)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A POLISH ORAL HISTORY PROJECT
    $39,000.00;$.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08250890), 1982 August 01-1984 April 30 (Reel R4807)
    TO SUPPORT KAZIMIERZ BRANDYS AS A WRITER-IN-RESIDENCE DURING ACADEMIC YEAR 1982-83
    $43,800.00;$43,800.00
    Poland; United States
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08251032), 1982 August 01-1982 December 31 (Reel R3688)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A COMPARATIVE STUDY OF YOUTH EMPLOYMENT PROGRAMS IN ENGLAND, FRANCE AND THE UNITED STATES
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08300179), 1983 January 15-1985 April 14 (Reel R4535)
    SUPPORT FOR ANALYSIS OF IMPACT OF CHANGING TECHNOLOGIES ON ENTRY LEVEL JOB AVAILABILITY AND TRAINING REQUIREMENTS
    $322,100.00;$322,100.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08300666), 1983 July 01-1992 June 30 (Reel R6593, Reel R6594, Reel R6595, Reel R7247)
    $3,125,000.00;$3,125,000.00
    Hecht, Jonathan;Harkness, James S.
    China; Legal services--China; Law --Study and teaching--China
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08350084), 1982 November 01-1983 October 31 (Reel R4072, Reel R4853)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "RETHINKING NORTH-SOUTH NEGOTIATIONS"
    $44,000.00;$44,000.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08350171), 1983 January 01-1983 December 31 (Reel R4245, Reel R5314)
    SUPPORT FOR A MEETING TO DISCUSS PROBLEMS IN U.S.-NICARAGUAN RELATIONS
    $13,140.00;$13,140.00
    Nicaragua
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08350271), 1983 February 01-1983 September 30 (Reel R4581)
    SUPPORT FOR A PLANNING CONFERENCE ON LEGAL EDUCATION EXCHANGES WITH THE PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC OF CHINA
    $55,736.00;$55,736.00
    McGuinness, Karen
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08350482), 1983 June 01-1984 May 31 (Reel R5130)
    MEETINGS ORGANIZED BY THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF HUMAN RIGHTS TO PROMOTE INTERNATIONAL COLLABORATION IN HUMAN RIGHTS RESEARCH
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08350726), 1983 August 01-1984 April 30 (Reel R4236)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON THE CURRENT SITUATION IN CENTRAL AMERICA
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08351010), 1983 November 01-1986 July 31 (Reel R4599)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON GENERAL EQUILIBRIUM TRADE POLICY MODELLING
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08351014), 1983 October 01-1985 August 31 (Reel R4679)
    FOR INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE THAT WILL APPLY RECENT ORAL HISTORY TECHNIQUES TO INTERNATIONAL RESEARCH ON WOMEN
    $4,035.00;$4,035.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08400288), 1984 January 01-1989 December 31 (Reel R5709)
    RESEARCH/TRAINING PROJECT ON PSYCHOLOGICAL DIMENSIONS OF US-SOVIET RELATIONS/IMPLICA FOR WESTERN INFLUENCE ON SOVIET SECURITY POLICY
    $280,910.00;$280,870.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08400342), 1984 January 01-1988 October 31 (Reel R5944)
    RESEARCH AND TRAINING ON REGIONAL SECURITY IN THE SOUTHERN RIM OF ASIA
    $282,200.00;$282,200.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08400470), 1984 August 01-1986 May 31 (Reel R5598)
    SUPPORT FOR AN INTERNATIONAL WORKING CONFERENCE ON CHILD SUPPORT
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08450496), 1984 June 01-1986 May 31 (Reel R4851)
    RESEARCH ON U.S. TRADE POLICY
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08450619), 1984 July 01-1984 December 31 (Reel R4880, Reel R5200)
    SUPPORT RESEARCH AND DOCUMENTATION IN HUMAN RIGHTS IN THE MIDDLE EAST
    $7,835.00;$7,835.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08450939), 1984 September 01-1987 May 31 (Reel R5485)
    STUDY OF THE CHURCH ROLE IN PROVIDING SERVICES TO NEWCOMERS AND IN SUPPORTING THEIR SELF-HELP PROJECTS
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08450940), 1984 September 01-1986 December 31 (Reel R4915)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH RELATING TO UNIVERSAL PRENATAL CARE IN THE UNITED STATES
    $40,800.00;$40,800.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08450961), 1985 March 01-1986 May 31 (Reel R4925)
    SUPPORT FOR AN ETHNOGRAPHIC STUDY ON CONFLICT AND COLLABORATION BETWEEN NEWCOMERS AND ESTABLISHED AMERICANS IN ONE N.Y. COMMUNITY
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08500222), 1985 January 01-1989 September 30 (Reel R5715)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT, "EDUCATIONAL SIMULATION OF U.S. FOREIGN POLICY"
    $158,916.00;$158,916.00
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08500578), 1985 May 01-1986 October 31 (Reel R4821)
    RESEARCH PROJECT RE "TRENDS IN PUBLIC OPINION TOWARD SOCIAL WELFARE POLICY" (WELFARE STATE)
    $9,360.00;$9,360.00
    O'Connor, Alice
  - The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York (08550130), 1984 October 01-1985 August 31 (Reel R5255, Reel R5531)
    SUPPORT FOR A DECEMBER 1984 CONFERENCE ON SOCIAL CHANGE IN BRAZIL SINCE 1945
    Fry, Peter